<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1.2.x To 1.3.x Upgrade Process on Cray System Management (CSM)</title>
    <link>/docs-csm/en-13/upgrade/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1.2.x To 1.3.x Upgrade Process on Cray System Management (CSM)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 03:18:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/docs-csm/en-13/upgrade/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade Automation</title>
      <link>/docs-csm/en-13/upgrade/scripts/upgrade/upgrade_automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 03:18:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs-csm/en-13/upgrade/scripts/upgrade/upgrade_automation/</guid>
      <description>Upgrade Automation This document describes how the CSM upgrade process is automated.
Overview In a nutshell, an upgrade is:
 Upload new artifacts into a running system. Rebuild each NCN with the newly uploaded images. Deploy new charts after all NCNs are upgraded.  Prerequisites Everything that is needed before upgrading an NCN.
 NOTE:
The prerequisites.sh script is required to run on both ncn-m001 and ncn-m002 (at different points in the upgrade process).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.2.0 Or Later To 1.3.0 Upgrade Process</title>
      <link>/docs-csm/en-13/upgrade/upgrade_management_nodes_and_csm_services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 03:18:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs-csm/en-13/upgrade/upgrade_management_nodes_and_csm_services/</guid>
      <description>CSM 1.2.0 or later to 1.3.0 Upgrade Process Introduction This document guides an administrator through the upgrade of Cray Systems Management from v1.0 to v1.2. When upgrading a system, follow this top-level file from top to bottom. The content on this top-level page is meant to be terse. For additional reference material on the upgrade processes and scripts mentioned explicitly on this page, see resource material.
Important Notes Service request adjustments are needed for small systems   For systems with only three worker nodes (typically Testing and Development Systems (TDS)), prior to proceeding with this upgrade, CPU limits MUST be lowered on several services in order for this upgrade to succeed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prepare For Upgrade</title>
      <link>/docs-csm/en-13/upgrade/prepare_for_upgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 03:18:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs-csm/en-13/upgrade/prepare_for_upgrade/</guid>
      <description>Prepare For Upgrade Before beginning an upgrade to a new version of CSM, there are a few things to do on the system first.
 Reduced resiliency during upgrade Export Nexus data Disable encryption for upgrade if enabled Start typescript Running sessions Health validation Stop typescript Preparation completed  Reduced resiliency during upgrade Warning: Management service resiliency is reduced during the upgrade.
Although it is expected that compute nodes and application nodes will continue to provide their services without interruption, it is important to be aware that the degree of management services resiliency is reduced during the upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stage 1 - Ceph Image Upgrade</title>
      <link>/docs-csm/en-13/upgrade/stage_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 03:18:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs-csm/en-13/upgrade/stage_1/</guid>
      <description>Stage 1 - Ceph image upgrade Reminder: If any problems are encountered and the procedure or command output does not provide relevant guidance, see Relevant troubleshooting links for upgrade-related issues.
 Stage 1 - Ceph image upgrade  Start typescript Run Ceph Latency Repair Script Apply boot order workaround Argo workflows CSM Upgrade requirement for upgrades staying within a CSM release version Storage node image upgrade Ensure that rbd stats monitoring is enabled Stop typescript Stage completed    Start typescript   (ncn-m001#) If a typescript session is already running in the shell, then first stop it with the exit command.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stage 2 - Kubernetes Upgrade</title>
      <link>/docs-csm/en-13/upgrade/stage_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 03:18:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs-csm/en-13/upgrade/stage_2/</guid>
      <description>Stage 2 - Kubernetes Upgrade Reminder: If any problems are encountered and the procedure or command output does not provide relevant guidance, see Relevant troubleshooting links for upgrade-related issues.
 Start typescript on ncn-m001 Stage 2.1 - Master node image upgrade Argo workflows Stage 2.2 - Worker node image upgrade  Option 1 - Serial upgrade Option 2 - Parallel upgrade (Tech preview)  Restrictions Example     Stage 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stage 3 - Service Upgrades</title>
      <link>/docs-csm/en-13/upgrade/stage_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 03:18:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs-csm/en-13/upgrade/stage_3/</guid>
      <description>Stage 3 - CSM Service Upgrades Reminder: If any problems are encountered and the procedure or command output does not provide relevant guidance, see Relevant troubleshooting links for upgrade-related issues.
 Start typescript Perform upgrade Verify Keycloak users Take Etcd Manual Backup Stop typescript Stage completed  Start typescript   (ncn-m002#) If a typescript session is already running in the shell, then first stop it with the exit command.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stage 4 - Ceph Upgrade</title>
      <link>/docs-csm/en-13/upgrade/stage_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 03:18:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs-csm/en-13/upgrade/stage_4/</guid>
      <description>Stage 4 - Ceph Upgrade Important: Ceph does not need to be upgraded if this is an upgrade is staying within a CSM release, e.g. CSM-1.3.0-rc1 to CSM-1.3.0-rc2. If this is an upgrade staying within a CSM release, then Ceph is already running v16.2.9. See instructions in stage completed for next steps.
Reminder: If any problems are encountered and the procedure or command output does not provide relevant guidance, then see Relevant troubleshooting links for upgrade-related issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.2.x To 1.3.x Upgrade Process</title>
      <link>/docs-csm/en-13/upgrade/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 03:18:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs-csm/en-13/upgrade/readme/</guid>
      <description>CSM 1.2.x to 1.3.x Upgrade Process The process for upgrading Cray Systems Management (CSM) has many steps in multiple procedures which should be done in a specific order.
After the upgrade of CSM software, the CSM health checks will validate the system before doing any other operational tasks like the check and update of firmware on system components. Once the CSM upgrade has completed, other product streams for the HPE Cray EX system can be installed or upgraded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stage 0 - Prerequisites And Preflight Checks</title>
      <link>/docs-csm/en-13/upgrade/stage_0_prerequisites/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 03:18:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs-csm/en-13/upgrade/stage_0_prerequisites/</guid>
      <description>Stage 0 - Prerequisites and Preflight Checks  Reminders:
 CSM 1.2.0 or higher is required in order to upgrade to CSM 1.3.0. If any problems are encountered and the procedure or command output does not provide relevant guidance, see Relevant troubleshooting links for upgrade-related issues.   Stage 0 has several critical procedures which prepare the environment and verify if the environment is ready for the upgrade.
 Start typescript Stage 0.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
