<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1.2.2 on Cray System Management (CSM)</title>
    <link>/docs-csm/en-12/upgrade/1.2.2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1.2.2 on Cray System Management (CSM)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 03:18:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/docs-csm/en-12/upgrade/1.2.2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1.2.2 Patch Installation Instructions</title>
      <link>/docs-csm/en-12/upgrade/1.2.2/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 03:18:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs-csm/en-12/upgrade/1.2.2/readme/</guid>
      <description>CSM 1.2.2 Patch Installation Instructions Introduction This document guides an administrator through the patch update to Cray Systems Management v1.2.2 from v1.2.0 or 1.2.1. If upgrading from CSM v1.0.x directly to v1.2.2, follow the procedures described in Upgrade CSM instead.
Bug Fixes and Improvements  Fixes the incorrect AppVersion that was being reported from csi version report Fixes speed with which the pods are restarted as a part of the precache chart upgrade (for better performance) Increases the timeout for the etcd_database_health check in the ncn-healthcheck Fixes issue with postgres database backups that caused them to fail to restore and cleans up existing (bad) postgres backups on the system Fixes the pod anti-affinity settings and pod disruption budget settings for cray-dns-unbound Fixes problem with unbound forwarding to powerDNS in an air-gapped environment Fixes a race condition between MEDS adding the initial BMC entries and Kea dhcp-helper logic updating IP addresses Fixes an issue where snmp credentials being set on leaf switches were being lost Fixes an issue where cray-hmcollector-poll pod was not collecting river telemetry due to a check the collector does against the SMA kafka instance Fixes CVEs in container images Limits Keycloak access (via ingress OPA policy) to well known OIDC endpoints for Shasta realm and only allow Keycloak administration through CMN Adds remediation for CVE-2020-10770 for keycloak Fixes issue with missing App.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade And Validate Switch Configurations</title>
      <link>/docs-csm/en-12/upgrade/1.2.2/upgrade_network/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 03:18:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs-csm/en-12/upgrade/1.2.2/upgrade_network/</guid>
      <description>Upgrade and validate Switch Configurations Prerequisites  SSH access to the switches or the running configuration file Upgrade or install latest version of CANU Install/Upgrade CANU  Run canu --version to see version CANU installed with version 1.6.13 or greater.   Use the paddle file (CCJ) if available, or validate an up-to-date SHCD Validate SHCD System Layout Service (SLS) input file. Collect Data   CAUTION: All of these steps should be done using an out-of-band connection.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
